<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>META on 壊れかけのエンジニアのログ</title>
    <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/tags/meta/</link>
    <description>Recent content in META on 壊れかけのエンジニアのログ</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ja</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 20:59:04 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/tags/meta/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>META_2023_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/meta_2023_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 20:59:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/meta_2023_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Dave, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to the Meta First Quarter Earnings Conference Call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers&amp;rsquo; remarks, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] This call will be recorded. Thank you very much. Ms. Deborah Crawford, Meta&amp;rsquo;s Vice President of Investor Relations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META_2022_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/meta_2022_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 20:43:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/meta_2022_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Dave and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to the Meta Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2022 Earnings Conference Call. [Operator Instructions] This call will be recorded. Thank you very much. Ms. Deborah Crawford, Meta’s Vice President of Investor Relations, you may begin.
Deborah Crawford: Thank you. Good afternoon and welcome to Meta Platform’s fourth quarter 2022 earnings conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META_2022_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/meta_2022_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 21:20:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/meta_2022_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Martin and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to the Meta Third Quarter Earnings Conference Call. [Operator Instructions] This call will be recorded. Thank you very much. Ms. Deborah Crawford, Meta’s Vice President of Investor Relations, you may begin.
Deborah Crawford: Thank you. Good afternoon and welcome to Meta Platforms third quarter 2022 earnings conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META_2022_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/meta_2022_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 09:50:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/meta_2022_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is France, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to the Meta&amp;rsquo;s second quarter earnings conference call. [Operator Instructions] This call will be recorded. Thank you very much. Ms. Deborah Crawford, Meta&amp;rsquo;s Vice President of Investor Relations, you may begin.
Deborah Crawford: Thank you. Good afternoon, and welcome to Meta Platform&amp;rsquo;s Second Quarter 2022 Earnings Conference Call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META_2022_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/meta_2022_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 22:03:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/meta_2022_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is France and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to the Meta First Quarter Earnings Conference Call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers’ remarks, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] The call will also be recorded. Thank you very much. Ms. Deborah Crawford, Meta’s Vice President of Investor Relations, you may begin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META_2021_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/meta_2021_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 20:36:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/meta_2021_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Frans, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to the Meta Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2021 Earnings Conference Call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers’ remarks, there will be a question-and-answer session. . The call will be recorded. Thank you very much. Ms. Deborah Crawford, Facebook Vice President of Investor Relations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META_2021_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/meta_2021_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 21:08:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/meta_2021_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is France, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to the Facebook Third Quarter 2021 earnings conference call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speaker’s remarks, there will be a question-and-answer session. keypad. This call will be recorded. Thank you very much. Ms. Deborah Crawford Facebook Vice President of Investor Relations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META_2021_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/meta_2021_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:20:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/meta_2021_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is France [ph], and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to the Facebook Second Quarter 2021 Earnings Conference Call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers&amp;rsquo; remarks, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] This call will be recorded. We thank you very much. Ms. Deborah Crawford, Facebook&amp;rsquo;s Vice President of Investor Relations, you may begin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META_2021_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/meta_2021_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 21:04:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/meta_2021_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is France, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to Facebook First Quarter 2021 Earnings Conference Call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers’ remarks, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] This call will be recorded. Thank you very much. Ms. Deborah Crawford, Facebook&amp;rsquo;s Vice President of Investor Relations, you may begin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META_2020_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/meta_2020_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 20:50:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/meta_2020_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Mike, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to the Facebook Fourth Quarter and Full-Year 2020 Earnings Conference Call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers’ remarks, there’ll be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] This call will be recorded. Thank you very much. Ms. Deborah Crawford, Facebook’s Vice President of Investor Relations, you may begin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META_2020_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/meta_2020_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 00:56:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/meta_2020_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Mike and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to the Facebook Third Quarter 2020 Earnings Conference Call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers’ remarks there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] This call will be recorded. Thank you very much. Ms. Deborah Crawford, Facebook’s Vice President of Investor Relations, you may begin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META_2020_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/meta_2020_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 22:24:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/meta_2020_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Mike and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to the Facebook Second Quarter 2020 Earnings Conference Call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers’ remarks, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] This call will be recorded. Thanks very much. Ms. Deborah Crawford, Facebook’s Vice President of Investor Relations, you may begin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META_2020_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/meta_2020_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 23:56:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/meta_2020_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon, my name is Mike and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to the Facebook First Quarter 2020 Earnings Conference Call. [Operator Instructions] Ms. Deborah Crawford, Facebook&amp;rsquo;s Vice President of Investor Relations, you may begin.
Deborah Crawford: Thank you. Good afternoon and welcome to Facebook&amp;rsquo;s first quarter 2020 earnings conference call. Joining me today to discuss our results are Mark Zuckerberg, CEO; Sheryl Sandberg, COO; and Dave Wehner, CFO.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
