<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MSFT on 壊れかけのエンジニアのログ</title>
    <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/tags/msft/</link>
    <description>Recent content in MSFT on 壊れかけのエンジニアのログ</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ja</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 21:15:21 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/tags/msft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2023_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/04/msft_2023_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 21:15:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/04/msft_2023_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Greetings, and welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2023 Third Quarter Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. A question-and-answer session will follow the formal presentation. [Operator Instructions] As a reminder, this conference is being recorded. I would now like to turn the conference over to your host, Brett Iversen, Vice President of Investor Relations. Please go ahead. Brett Iversen: Good afternoon, and thank you for joining us today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2023_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/01/msft_2023_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 21:24:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/01/msft_2023_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Greetings and welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2023 Second Quarter Earnings Conference Call. [Operator Instructions] As a reminder, this conference is being recorded. I would now like to turn the conference over to your host, Brett Iversen, Vice President, Investor Relations. Brett Iversen: Good afternoon and thank you for joining us today. On the call with me are Satya Nadella, Chairman and Chief Executive Officer; Amy Hood, Chief Financial Officer; Alice Jolla, Chief Accounting Officer; and Keith Dolliver, Deputy General Counsel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2023_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/10/msft_2023_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 19:05:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/10/msft_2023_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Greetings, and welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2023 First Quarter Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. A question-and-answer session will follow the formal presentation. [Operator Instructions] As a reminder, this conference is being recorded. It is now my pleasure to introduce your host, Mr. Brett Iversen, Vice President, Investor Relations. Thank you. You may begin. Brett Iversen: Good afternoon, and thank you for joining us today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2022_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/07/msft_2022_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 20:07:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/07/msft_2022_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Greetings, and welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2022 Fourth Quarter Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. A question-and-answer session will follow the formal presentation. [Operator Instructions] As a reminder, this conference is being recorded. It is now my pleasure to introduce your host, Brett Iversen, Vice President of Investor Relations. Thank you. You may begin. Brett Iversen: Good afternoon, and thank you for joining us today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2022_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/04/msft_2022_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 21:20:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/04/msft_2022_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Ladies and gentlemen thank you for standing by. Welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2022 Third Quarter Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. A question-and-answer session will follow the formal presentation. [Operator Instructions] As a reminder, this conference is being recorded. It is now my pleasure to introduce your host, Brett Iversen, General Manager, Investor Relations. Thank you. You may begin. Brett Iversen: Good afternoon and thank you for joining us today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2022_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/01/msft_2022_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 20:51:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/01/msft_2022_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Greetings, and welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2022 Second Quarter Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. A question-and-answer session will follow the formal presentation. [Operator Instructions] As a reminder, this conference is being recorded. It is now my pleasure to introduce your host, Brett Iversen, General Manager, Investor Relations. Thank you. You may begin. Brett Iversen: Good afternoon, and thank you for joining us today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2022_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/10/msft_2022_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 21:19:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/10/msft_2022_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Greetings and welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2022, First-Quarter earnings conference call. As a reminder, this conference is being recorded. It is now my pleasure to introduce your host, Brett Iversen, General Manager and Investor Relations. Thank you, you may begin. Brett Iversen: Good afternoon, and thank you for joining us today. On the call with me are Satya Nadella, Chairman Chief Executive Officer, Amy Hood, Chief Financial Officer, Alice Jalla, Chief Accounting Officer, and Keith Dolliver, Deputy General Counsel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2021_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/07/msft_2021_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 21:36:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/07/msft_2021_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Greetings, and welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2021 Fourth Quarter Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. A question-and-answer session will follow the formal presentation. [Operator Instructions] As a reminder, this conference is being recorded. It is now my pleasure to introduce your host, Brett Iversen, General Manager of Investor Relations. Thank you. You may begin. Brett Iversen: Good afternoon and thank you for joining us today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2021_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/04/msft_2021_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 23:42:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/04/msft_2021_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Greetings, and welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2021 Third Quarter Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. A question-and-answer session will follow the formal presentation. [Operator Instructions] And as a reminder, this conference is being recorded. It is now my pleasure to introduce your host, Brett Iversen, General Manager, Investor Relations. Thank you. You may begin. Brett Iversen: Good afternoon, and thank you for joining us today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2021_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/01/msft_2021_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 22:56:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/01/msft_2021_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Greetings, and welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2021 Second Quarter Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. A brief question-and-answer session will follow the formal presentation. [Operator Instructions] As a reminder, this conference is being recorded. It is now my pleasure to introduce your host, Mike Spencer, General Manager, Investor Relations. Thank you, sir. You may begin. Michael Spencer: Good afternoon, and thank you for joining us today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2021_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/10/msft_2021_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 21:15:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/10/msft_2021_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Greetings, and welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2021 First Quarter Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. A question-and-answer session will follow the formal presentation. [Operator Instructions] As a reminder, this conference is being recorded. It is now my pleasure to introduce your host, Michael Spencer, General Manager, Investor Relations. Thank you. You may begin. Michael Spencer: Good afternoon and thank you for joining us today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2020_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/07/msft_2020_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 21:28:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/07/msft_2020_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Greetings, and welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2020 Fourth Quarter Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. A question-and-answer session will follow the former presentation. [Operator Instructions] As a reminder, this conference is being recorded. It is now my pleasure to introduce your host, Mike Spencer, General Manager and Investor Relations for Microsoft. Thank you, sir. You may begin. Mike Spencer: Good afternoon and thank you for joining us today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2020_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/04/msft_2020_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 23:01:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/04/msft_2020_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Greetings, and welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2020 Third Quarter Earnings Conference Call. [Operator Instructions]. As a reminder, this conference is being recorded. I would now like to turn the conference over to your host, Mr. Mike Spencer, General Manager of Investor Relations for Microsoft. Thank you. You may begin. Michael Spencer: Good afternoon, and thank you for joining us today. On the call with me are Satya Nadella, Chief Executive Officer; Amy Hood, Chief Financial Officer; Frank Brod, Chief Accounting Officer; and Keith Dolliver, Deputy General Counsel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2020_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/01/msft_2020_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 21:38:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/01/msft_2020_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2020 Second Quarter Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. A brief question-and-answer session will follow the formal presentation. [Operator Instructions] As a reminder, this conference is being recorded. I would like to turn the call over to Mike Spencer, General Manager of Investor Relations. Thank you. Please proceed. Mike Spencer: Good afternoon and thank you for joining us today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2020_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2019/10/msft_2020_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 22:19:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2019/10/msft_2020_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2020 First Quarter Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. A brief question-and-answer session will follow the formal presentation. [Operator Instructions] As a reminder, this conference is being recorded. I would like to turn the call over to Mike Spencer, General Manager of Investor Relations. Thank you. Please proceed. Mike Spencer: Good afternoon. Thank you for joining us today.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
