<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NVDA on 壊れかけのエンジニアのログ</title>
    <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/tags/nvda/</link>
    <description>Recent content in NVDA on 壊れかけのエンジニアのログ</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ja</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 19:33:12 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/tags/nvda/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2023_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/02/nvda_2023_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 19:33:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/02/nvda_2023_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Emma, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to the NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s Fourth Quarter Earnings Call. [Operator Instructions]. Thank you. Simona Jankowski, you may begin your conference.
Simona Jankowski: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s conference call for the fourth quarter of fiscal 2023. With me today from NVIDIA are Jensen Huang, President and Chief Executive Officer; and Colette Kress, Executive Vice President and Chief Financial Officer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2023_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/11/nvda_2023_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 21:24:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/11/nvda_2023_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Emma, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to NVIDIA’s Third Quarter Earnings Call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers’ remarks, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] Simona Jankowski, you may begin your conference.
Simona Jankowski: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to NVIDIA’s conference call for the third quarter of fiscal 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2023_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/08/nvda_2023_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 21:22:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/08/nvda_2023_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Regina, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to NVIDIA’s Second Quarter Earnings Call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers’ remarks, there will be question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] [Technical Difficulty]
Simona Jankowski: Conference call for the second quarter of fiscal 2023. With me today from NVIDIA are Jensen Huang, President and Chief Executive Officer; and Colette Kress, Executive Vice President and Chief Financial Officer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2023_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/05/nvda_2023_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 19:24:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/05/nvda_2023_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is David, and I&amp;rsquo;ll be your conference operator today. At this time, I&amp;rsquo;d like to welcome everyone to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s first quarter earnings call. Today&amp;rsquo;s conference is being recorded. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speaker’s remarks, there will be question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] Thank you. Simona Jankowski, you may begin your conference.
Simona Jankowski: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s conference call for the First Quarter of Fiscal 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2022_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/02/nvda_2022_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 22:12:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/02/nvda_2022_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is David, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I&amp;rsquo;d like to welcome everyone to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s Fourth Quarter Earnings Call. Today&amp;rsquo;s conference is being recorded. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers’ remarks, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions]. Thank you. Simona Jankowski, you may begin your conference.
Simona Jankowski: Thank you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2022_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/08/nvda_2022_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 22:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/08/nvda_2022_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Mel, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s Second Quarter Earnings Call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers&amp;rsquo; remarks, there will be a question and answer session. [Operator Instructions] Thank you. Simona Jankowski, you may begin your conference.
Simona Jankowski: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2022_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/05/nvda_2022_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 23:46:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/05/nvda_2022_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Sumitra, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to the NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s Financial Results Conference Call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers&amp;rsquo; remarks, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] Thank you. Simona Jankowski, you may begin your conference.
Simona Jankowski: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s conference call for the first quarter of fiscal 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2021_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/02/nvda_2021_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 23:44:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/02/nvda_2021_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Mariama, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s Financial Results Conference Call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers&amp;rsquo; remarks, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] Thank you. I will now turn the call over to Simona Jankowski, NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s Vice President of Investor Relations and Strategic Finance to begin the conference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2021_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/11/nvda_2021_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 21:53:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/11/nvda_2021_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Jason, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to NVIDIA’s Third Quarter Financial Results Conference Call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers’ remarks, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] Thank you. Simona Jankowski, you may begin your conference.
Simona Jankowski: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone and welcome to NVIDIA’s conference call for the third quarter of fiscal 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2021_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/08/nvda_2021_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 02:03:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/08/nvda_2021_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is David and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to NVIDIA’s Financial Results Conference Call. [Operator Instructions] Thank you. Simona Jankowski, you may begin your conference.
Simona Jankowski: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone and welcome to NVIDIA’s conference call for the second quarter of fiscal 2021. With me on the call today from NVIDIA are Jensen Huang, President and Chief Executive Officer and Colette Kress, Executive Vice President and Chief Financial Officer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2021_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/05/nvda_2021_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 04:29:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/05/nvda_2021_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Josh, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s Financial Results Conference call. [Operator Instructions]. Simona Jankowski, you may begin your conference.
Simona Jankowski: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s conference call for the first quarter of fiscal 2021. With me on the call today from NVIDIA are Jensen Huang, President and Chief Executive Officer; and Colette Kress, Executive Vice President and Chief Financial Officer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2020_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/02/nvda_2020_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 21:46:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/02/nvda_2020_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Christina and I&amp;rsquo;m your conference operator today. Welcome to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s financial results conference call. All lines have been placed on mute. After the speakers&amp;rsquo; remarks, there will be question-and-answer period. [Operator Instructions] Thank you. I&amp;rsquo;ll now turn the call over to Simona Jankowski, Vice President of Investor Relations, to begin your conference.
Simona Jankowski: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s conference call for the fourth quarter of fiscal 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2020_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2019/11/nvda_2020_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 21:12:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2019/11/nvda_2020_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Christina, and I&amp;rsquo;m your conference operator for today. Welcome to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s Financial Results Conference Call. [Operator Instructions]. I&amp;rsquo;ll now turn the call over to Simona Jankowski, Vice President of Investor Relations, to begin your conference.
Simona Jankowski: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s conference call for the third quarter of fiscal 2020. With me on the call today from NVIDIA are Jensen Huang, President and Chief Executive Officer; and Colette Kress, Executive Vice President and Chief Financial Officer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2020_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2019/08/nvda_2020_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 08:42:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2019/08/nvda_2020_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Christina, and I will be your conference operator today. Welcome to NVIDIA’s financial results conference call. [Operator Instructions] I will now turn the call over to Simona Jankowski from Investor Relations to begin your conference.
Simona Jankowski: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone and welcome to NVIDIA’s conference call for the second quarter of fiscal 2020. With me on the call today from NVIDIA are Jen-Hsun Huang, President and Chief Executive Officer and Colette Kress, Executive Vice President and Chief Financial Officer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2020_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2019/05/nvda_2020_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 23:49:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2019/05/nvda_2020_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Kristina, and I&amp;rsquo;ll be your conference operator today. Welcome to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s financial results conference call. All lines have been placed on mute. [Operator Instructions] I&amp;rsquo;ll now turn the call over to Simona Jankowski from Investor Relations to begin your conference.
Simona Jankowski: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone. And welcome to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s conference call for the first quarter of fiscal 2020. With me on the call today from NVIDIA are Jen-Hsun Huang, President and Chief Executive Officer and Colette Kress, Executive Vice President and Chief Financial Officer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
