<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GOOG on 壊れかけのエンジニアのログ</title>
    <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/tags/goog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in GOOG on 壊れかけのエンジニアのログ</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ja</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 21:17:02 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/tags/goog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GOOG_2023_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/goog_2023_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 21:17:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/goog_2023_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Welcome, everyone. Thank you for standing by for the Alphabet First Quarter 2023 Earnings Conference Call. [Operator Instructions] I would now like to hand the conference over to your speaker today, Jim Friedland, Director of Investor Relations. Please go ahead.
Jim Friedland: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone and welcome to Alphabet’s first quarter 2023 earnings conference call. With us today are Sundar Pichai, Philipp Schindler and Ruth Porat. Now I will quickly cover the Safe Harbor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG_2022_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/goog_2022_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 18:10:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/goog_2022_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Welcome, everyone. Thank you for standing by for the Alphabet Fourth Quarter 2022 Earnings Conference Call. At this time all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the speaker presentation, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] I would now like to hand the conference over to your speaker today, Jim Friedland, Director of Investor Relations. Please, go ahead.
Jim Friedland: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s fourth quarter 2022 earnings conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG_2022_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/goog_2022_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 19:51:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/goog_2022_q3/</guid>
      <description>Jim Friedland: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to Alphabet’s third quarter 2022 earnings conference call. With us today are Sundar Pichai, Philipp Schindler and Ruth Porat. Now, I’ll quickly cover the safe harbor. Some of the statements that we make today regarding our business, operations and financial performance may be considered forward-looking, and such statements involve a number of risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG_2022_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/goog_2022_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 20:47:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/goog_2022_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Welcome, everyone, and thank you for standing by for the Alphabet Inc. Second Quarter 2022 Earnings Call. At this time all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the speakers’ presentation, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] I would now like to hand the conference over to your speaker today, Jim Friedland, Director of Investor Relations. Please go ahead.
Jim Friedland: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to Alphabet’s second quarter 2022 earnings conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG_2022_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/goog_2022_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 21:59:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/goog_2022_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Welcome, everyone, and thank you for standing by for the Alphabet First Quarter 2022 Earnings Conference Call. [Operator Instructions] I&amp;rsquo;d now like to hand the conference over to your speaker today, Jim Friedland, Director of Investor Relations. Please go ahead.
James Friedland: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s first quarter 2022 earnings conference call. With us today are Sundar Pichai, Philipp Schindler and Ruth Porat. Now I&amp;rsquo;ll quickly cover the safe harbor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG_2021_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/goog_2021_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 21:11:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/goog_2021_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Welcome, everyone, and thank you for standing by for the Alphabet Fourth Quarter 2021 Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the speakers’ presentation, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions]. I&amp;rsquo;d now like to hand the conference over to your speaker today, Jim Friedland, Director of Investor Relations. Please go ahead.
James Friedland: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s fourth quarter 2021 earnings conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG_2021_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/goog_2021_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 20:10:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/goog_2021_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Welcome everyone, and thank you for standing by for the Alphabet Q3 2021 Earnings C conference Call. At this time, all participants are in listen-only mode. After the speaker presentation, there will be a question-and-answer session. I&amp;rsquo;d now like to turn the conference over to your speaker today, Jim Friedland, Director of Investor Relations. Please go ahead.
Jim Friedland: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s third quarter 2021 earnings conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG_2021_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/goog_2021_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 22:55:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/goog_2021_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Welcome, everyone. Thank you for standing by for the Alphabet Second Quarter 2021 Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the speakers’ presentation, there will be a question-and-answer session. I would now like to hand the conference over to your speaker today, Jim Friedland, Director of Investor Relations. Please go ahead.
Jim Friedland: Thank you. Good afternoon everyone and welcome to Alphabet’s second quarter earnings conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG_2021_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/goog_2021_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 23:05:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/goog_2021_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Welcome, everyone, and thank you for standing by for the Alphabet First Quarter 2021 Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the speakers’ presentation, there will be a question-and-answer session. I’d now like to hand the conference over to your speaker today, Jim Friedland, Director of Investor Relations. Please go ahead.
Jim Friedland: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to Alphabet’s first quarter 2021 earnings conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG_2020_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/goog_2020_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 20:14:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/goog_2020_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Welcome, everyone, and thank you for standing by for the Alphabet Fourth Quarter 2020 Earnings Conference Call. . I would now like to hand the conference over to your speaker today, Jim Friedland, Director of Investor Relations. Please go ahead.
James Friedland: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s Fourth Quarter 2020 Earnings Conference Call. With us today are Sundar Pichai, Philipp Schindler and Ruth Porat. Now I&amp;rsquo;ll quickly cover the safe harbor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG_2020_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/goog_2020_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 23:16:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/goog_2020_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for standing by, and welcome to the Alphabet Third Quarter 2020 Earnings Conference Call. At this time all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the speakers presentation, there will be a question-and-answer session. . I&amp;rsquo;d now like to hand the conference over to your speaker today, Jim Friedland, Director of Investor Relations. Please go ahead.
James Friedland: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s third quarter 2020 earnings conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG_2020_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/goog_2020_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 21:03:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/goog_2020_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for standing by, and welcome to the Alphabet Second Quarter 2020 Earnings Conference Call. . I&amp;rsquo;d now like to hand the conference over to your speaker today, Jim Friedland, Director of Investor Relations. Please go ahead.
James Friedland: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s second quarter 2020 earnings conference call. With us today are Sundar Pichai and Ruth Porat. Now I&amp;rsquo;ll quickly cover the safe harbor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG_2020_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/goog_2020_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 23:46:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/converted/transcript/goog_2020_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for standing by. And welcome to the Alphabet First Quarter 2020 Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the speakers’ presentation, there will be a question-and-answer session. I would now like to hand the conference over to your speaker today, Jim Friedland, Director of Investor Relations. Please go ahead.
Jim Friedland: Thank you, Candice. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to Alphabet’s first quarter 2020 earnings conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
