<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AMZN on 壊れかけのエンジニアのログ</title>
    <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/tags/amzn/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AMZN on 壊れかけのエンジニアのログ</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ja</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 19:55:02 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/tags/amzn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AMZN_2023_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/04/amzn_2023_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 19:55:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/04/amzn_2023_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good day, everyone, and welcome to the Amazon.com First Quarter 2023 Financial Results Teleconference. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the presentation, we will conduct a question-and-answer session. Today’s call is being recorded. For opening remarks, I will be turning the call over to the Vice President of Investor Relations, Dave Fildes. Thank you, sir. Please go ahead. Dave Fildes: Hello, and welcome to our Q1 2023 financial results conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN_2022_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/02/amzn_2022_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 21:26:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/02/amzn_2022_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Thank you for standing by. Good day, everyone, and welcome to the Amazon.com Quarter 4 2022 Financial Results Teleconference. [Operator Instructions]. And for opening remarks, I will be turning the call over to the Vice President of Investor Relations, Dave Fildes. Thank you, sir. Please go ahead. Dave Fildes: Hello, and welcome to our Q4 2022 financial results conference call. Joining us today to answer your questions is Andy Jassy, our CEO; and Brian Olsavsky, our CFO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN_2022_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/10/amzn_2022_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 19:55:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/10/amzn_2022_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good day, everyone, and welcome to the Amazon.com Q3 2022 Financial Results Teleconference. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the presentation, we will conduct a question-and-answer session. Today&amp;rsquo;s call is being recorded. For opening remarks, I will be turning the call over to the Vice President of Investor Relations, Dave Fildes. Thank you, sir. Please go ahead. Dave Fildes: Hello, and welcome to our Q3 2022 financial results conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN_2022_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/07/amzn_2022_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 21:06:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/07/amzn_2022_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Thank you for standing by. Good day, everyone, and welcome to the Amazon.com Q2 2022 Financial Results Teleconference. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the presentation, we will conduct a question-and-answer session. Today&amp;rsquo;s call is being recorded. For opening remarks, I will be turning the call over to the Director of Investor Relations, Dave Fildes. Please go ahead. Dave Fildes: Hello, and welcome to our Q2 2022 financial results conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN_2022_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/04/amzn_2022_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 20:27:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/04/amzn_2022_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Thank you for standing by. Good day, everyone, and welcome to the Amazon.com Q1 2022 Financial Results Teleconference. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the presentation, we will conduct a question-and-answer session. Today&amp;rsquo;s call is being recorded. For opening remarks, I will be turning the call over to the Director of Investor Relations, Dave Fildes. Please go ahead. Dave Fildes: Hello, and welcome to our Q1 2022 financial results conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN_2021_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/02/amzn_2021_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 19:50:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/02/amzn_2021_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Thank you for standing by. Good day, everyone, and welcome to the Amazon.com Q4 2021 Financial Results Teleconference. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the presentation, we will conduct a question-and-answer session. Today’s call is being recorded. For opening remarks, I will be turning the call over to the Director of Investor Relations, Dave Fildes. Please go ahead. Dave Fildes: Hello, and welcome to our Q4 2021 financial results conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN_2021_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/10/amzn_2021_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 23:14:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/10/amzn_2021_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Thank you for standing by. Good day, everyone, and welcome to the amazon.com Q3 2021 Financial Results Teleconference. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the presentation, we will conduct a question-and-answer session. Today&amp;rsquo;s call is being recorded. For opening remarks, I&amp;rsquo;ll be turning the call over to Director of Investor Relations, Dave Fildes. Please go ahead. Dave Fildes: Hello, and welcome to our Q3 2021 financial results conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN_2021_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/07/amzn_2021_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 20:51:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/07/amzn_2021_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Thank you for standing by. Good day, everyone, and welcome to the amazon.com Q2 2021 Financial Results, Teleconference. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the presentation, we will conduct a question-and-answer session. Today&amp;rsquo;s call is being recorded. For opening remarks, I will be turning the call over to Director of Investor Relations, Mr. Dave Fildes. Please go ahead. Dave Fildes: Hello, and welcome to our Q2 2021 financial results conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN_2021_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/04/amzn_2021_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 23:15:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/04/amzn_2021_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Thank you for standing by. Good day, everyone, and welcome to the Amazon.com Q1 2021 Financial Results Teleconference. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the presentation, we will conduct a question-and-answer session. Today&amp;rsquo;s call is being recorded. For opening remarks, I will be turning the call over to Director of Investor Relations, Mr. Dave Fildes. Please go ahead. Dave Fildes: Hello, and welcome to our Q1 2021 financial results conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN_2020_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/02/amzn_2020_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 23:25:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/02/amzn_2020_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Thank you for standing by. Good day, everyone and welcome to the Amazon.com Q4 2020 Financial Results Teleconference. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the presentation, we will conduct a question-and-answer session. Today’s call is being recorded. For opening remarks, I will be turning the call over to Director of Investor Relations, Dave Fildes. Please go ahead. Dave Fildes: Hello and welcome to our Q4 2020 financial results conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN_2020_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/10/amzn_2020_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 22:40:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/10/amzn_2020_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Thank you for standing by. Good day, everyone and welcome to the Amazon.com Q3 2020 Financial Results Teleconference. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the presentation, we will conduct a question-and-answer session. Today&amp;rsquo;s call is being recorded. For opening remarks, I will be turning the call over to Head of Investor Relations, Dave Fildes. Please go ahead. Dave Fildes: Hello and welcome to our Q3 2020 financial results conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN_2020_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/07/amzn_2020_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 22:42:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/07/amzn_2020_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Thank you for standing by. Good day, everyone, and welcome to the Amazon.com Q2 2020 Financial Results Teleconference. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the presentation, we will conduct a question-and-answer session. Today’s call is being recorded. For opening remarks, I will be turning the call over to Director of Investor Relations, David Fildes. Please go ahead. David Fildes: Hello, and welcome to our Q2 2020 financial results conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN_2020_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/04/amzn_2020_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 22:46:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/04/amzn_2020_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good day everyone and welcome to the Amazon.com Q1 2020 financial results teleconference. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the presentation we will conduct a question and answer session. Today&amp;rsquo;s call is being recorded. For opening remarks, I will be turning the call over to Director of Investor Relations, Shelly Kay Pfeiffer. Please go ahead. Shelly Kay Pfeiffer: Hello and welcome to our Q1 2020 financial results conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
