<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>earning call on 壊れかけのエンジニアのログ</title>
    <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/categories/earning-call/</link>
    <description>Recent content in earning call on 壊れかけのエンジニアのログ</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ja</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 21:35:32 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/categories/earning-call/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AAPL_2023_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/05/aapl_2023_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 21:35:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/05/aapl_2023_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good day, and welcome to the Apple’s Q2 Fiscal Year 2023 Earnings Conference Call. Today&amp;rsquo;s call is being recorded. At this time, for opening remarks and introductions, I would like to turn the call over to Suhasini Chandramouli, Director of Investor Relations. Please go ahead.
Suhasini Chandramouli : Thank you. Good afternoon and thank you for joining us. Speaking first today is Apple&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Tim Cook; and he&amp;rsquo;ll be followed by CFO, Luca Maestri.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN_2023_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/04/amzn_2023_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 19:55:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/04/amzn_2023_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good day, everyone, and welcome to the Amazon.com First Quarter 2023 Financial Results Teleconference. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the presentation, we will conduct a question-and-answer session. Today’s call is being recorded. For opening remarks, I will be turning the call over to the Vice President of Investor Relations, Dave Fildes. Thank you, sir. Please go ahead.
Dave Fildes: Hello, and welcome to our Q1 2023 financial results conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META_2023_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/04/meta_2023_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 20:59:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/04/meta_2023_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Dave, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to the Meta First Quarter Earnings Conference Call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers&amp;rsquo; remarks, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] This call will be recorded. Thank you very much. Ms. Deborah Crawford, Meta&amp;rsquo;s Vice President of Investor Relations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG_2023_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/04/goog_2023_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 21:17:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/04/goog_2023_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Welcome, everyone. Thank you for standing by for the Alphabet First Quarter 2023 Earnings Conference Call. [Operator Instructions] I would now like to hand the conference over to your speaker today, Jim Friedland, Director of Investor Relations. Please go ahead.
Jim Friedland: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone and welcome to Alphabet’s first quarter 2023 earnings conference call. With us today are Sundar Pichai, Philipp Schindler and Ruth Porat. Now I will quickly cover the Safe Harbor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2023_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/04/msft_2023_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 21:15:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/04/msft_2023_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Greetings, and welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2023 Third Quarter Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. A question-and-answer session will follow the formal presentation. [Operator Instructions] As a reminder, this conference is being recorded. I would now like to turn the conference over to your host, Brett Iversen, Vice President of Investor Relations. Please go ahead.
Brett Iversen: Good afternoon, and thank you for joining us today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSLA_2023_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/04/tsla_2023_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 18:54:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/04/tsla_2023_q1/</guid>
      <description>Martin Viecha: Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to Tesla&amp;rsquo;s First Quarter 2023 Q&amp;amp;A Webcast. My name is Martin Viecha, VP of Investor Relations and I&amp;rsquo;m joined today by Elon Musk, Zachary Kirkhorn, and a number of other executives. Our Q1 results were announced at about 3:00 P.M. Central Time in the update deck we published at the same link as this webcast. During this call, we will discuss our business outlook and make forward-looking statements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2023_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/02/nvda_2023_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 19:33:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/02/nvda_2023_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Emma, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to the NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s Fourth Quarter Earnings Call. [Operator Instructions]. Thank you. Simona Jankowski, you may begin your conference.
Simona Jankowski: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s conference call for the fourth quarter of fiscal 2023. With me today from NVIDIA are Jensen Huang, President and Chief Executive Officer; and Colette Kress, Executive Vice President and Chief Financial Officer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AAPL_2023_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/02/aapl_2023_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 21:33:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/02/aapl_2023_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good day, everyone, and welcome to the Apple Q1 Fiscal Year 2023 Earnings Conference Call. Today&amp;rsquo;s call is being recorded. And now at this time, for opening remarks and introductions, I would like to turn the call over to Tejas Gala, Director of Investor Relations and Corporate Finance. Please go ahead.
Tejas Gala: Thank you. Speaking first today is Apple&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Tim Cook; and he&amp;rsquo;ll be followed by CFO, Luca Maestri.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN_2022_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/02/amzn_2022_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 21:26:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/02/amzn_2022_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Thank you for standing by. Good day, everyone, and welcome to the Amazon.com Quarter 4 2022 Financial Results Teleconference. [Operator Instructions]. And for opening remarks, I will be turning the call over to the Vice President of Investor Relations, Dave Fildes. Thank you, sir. Please go ahead.
Dave Fildes: Hello, and welcome to our Q4 2022 financial results conference call. Joining us today to answer your questions is Andy Jassy, our CEO; and Brian Olsavsky, our CFO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG_2022_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/02/goog_2022_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 18:10:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/02/goog_2022_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Welcome, everyone. Thank you for standing by for the Alphabet Fourth Quarter 2022 Earnings Conference Call. At this time all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the speaker presentation, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] I would now like to hand the conference over to your speaker today, Jim Friedland, Director of Investor Relations. Please, go ahead.
Jim Friedland: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s fourth quarter 2022 earnings conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META_2022_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/02/meta_2022_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 20:43:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/02/meta_2022_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Dave and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to the Meta Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2022 Earnings Conference Call. [Operator Instructions] This call will be recorded. Thank you very much. Ms. Deborah Crawford, Meta’s Vice President of Investor Relations, you may begin.
Deborah Crawford: Thank you. Good afternoon and welcome to Meta Platform’s fourth quarter 2022 earnings conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSLA_2022_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/01/tsla_2022_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 19:33:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/01/tsla_2022_q4/</guid>
      <description>Martin Viecha: Good afternoon everyone and welcome to Tesla&amp;rsquo;s Fourth Quarter 2022 Q&amp;amp;A Webcast. My name is Martin Viecha, VP of Investor Relations and I&amp;rsquo;m joined today by Elon Musk, Zachary Kirkhorn and a number of other executives. Our Q4 results were announced at about 3:00 P.M. Central Time in the update deck we published at the same link as this webcast. During this call, we will discuss our business outlook and make forward-looking statements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2023_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/01/msft_2023_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 21:24:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2023/01/msft_2023_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Greetings and welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2023 Second Quarter Earnings Conference Call. [Operator Instructions] As a reminder, this conference is being recorded. I would now like to turn the conference over to your host, Brett Iversen, Vice President, Investor Relations.
Brett Iversen: Good afternoon and thank you for joining us today. On the call with me are Satya Nadella, Chairman and Chief Executive Officer; Amy Hood, Chief Financial Officer; Alice Jolla, Chief Accounting Officer; and Keith Dolliver, Deputy General Counsel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2023_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/11/nvda_2023_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 21:24:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/11/nvda_2023_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Emma, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to NVIDIA’s Third Quarter Earnings Call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers’ remarks, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] Simona Jankowski, you may begin your conference.
Simona Jankowski: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to NVIDIA’s conference call for the third quarter of fiscal 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN_2022_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/10/amzn_2022_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 19:55:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/10/amzn_2022_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good day, everyone, and welcome to the Amazon.com Q3 2022 Financial Results Teleconference. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the presentation, we will conduct a question-and-answer session. Today&amp;rsquo;s call is being recorded. For opening remarks, I will be turning the call over to the Vice President of Investor Relations, Dave Fildes. Thank you, sir. Please go ahead.
Dave Fildes: Hello, and welcome to our Q3 2022 financial results conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AAPL_2022_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/10/aapl_2022_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 19:46:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/10/aapl_2022_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good day, and welcome to the Apple Q4 Fiscal Year 2022 Earnings Conference Call. For your information, today&amp;rsquo;s call is being recorded. At this time, for opening remarks and introductions, I would like to turn the call over to Tejas Gala, Director of Investor Relations and Corporate Finance. Please go ahead.
Tejas Gala: Speaking first today is Apple&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Tim Cook; and he&amp;rsquo;ll be followed by CFO, Luca Maestri. After that, we&amp;rsquo;ll open the call to questions from analysts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META_2022_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/10/meta_2022_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 21:20:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/10/meta_2022_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Martin and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to the Meta Third Quarter Earnings Conference Call. [Operator Instructions] This call will be recorded. Thank you very much. Ms. Deborah Crawford, Meta’s Vice President of Investor Relations, you may begin.
Deborah Crawford: Thank you. Good afternoon and welcome to Meta Platforms third quarter 2022 earnings conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG_2022_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/10/goog_2022_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 19:51:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/10/goog_2022_q3/</guid>
      <description>Jim Friedland: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to Alphabet’s third quarter 2022 earnings conference call. With us today are Sundar Pichai, Philipp Schindler and Ruth Porat. Now, I’ll quickly cover the safe harbor. Some of the statements that we make today regarding our business, operations and financial performance may be considered forward-looking, and such statements involve a number of risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2023_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/10/msft_2023_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 19:05:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/10/msft_2023_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Greetings, and welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2023 First Quarter Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. A question-and-answer session will follow the formal presentation. [Operator Instructions] As a reminder, this conference is being recorded. It is now my pleasure to introduce your host, Mr. Brett Iversen, Vice President, Investor Relations. Thank you. You may begin.
Brett Iversen: Good afternoon, and thank you for joining us today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSLA_2022_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/10/tsla_2022_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 22:14:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/10/tsla_2022_q3/</guid>
      <description>Martin Viecha: Good afternoon, everyone and welcome to Tesla’s Third Quarter 2022 Q&amp;amp;A Webcast. My name is Martin Viecha, VP of Investor Relations and I am joined today by Elon Musk, Zachary Kirkhorn and a number of other executives. Our Q3 results were announced at about 3:00 p.m. Central Time in the update deck we published at the same link as this webcast. During the call, we will discuss our business outlook and make forward-looking statements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2023_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/08/nvda_2023_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 21:22:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/08/nvda_2023_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Regina, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to NVIDIA’s Second Quarter Earnings Call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers’ remarks, there will be question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] [Technical Difficulty]
Simona Jankowski: Conference call for the second quarter of fiscal 2023. With me today from NVIDIA are Jensen Huang, President and Chief Executive Officer; and Colette Kress, Executive Vice President and Chief Financial Officer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META_2022_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/07/meta_2022_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 09:50:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/07/meta_2022_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is France, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to the Meta&amp;rsquo;s second quarter earnings conference call. [Operator Instructions] This call will be recorded. Thank you very much. Ms. Deborah Crawford, Meta&amp;rsquo;s Vice President of Investor Relations, you may begin.
Deborah Crawford: Thank you. Good afternoon, and welcome to Meta Platform&amp;rsquo;s Second Quarter 2022 Earnings Conference Call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AAPL_2022_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/07/aapl_2022_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 21:11:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/07/aapl_2022_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good day, and welcome to the Apple Q3 FY 2022 Earnings Conference Call. Today&amp;rsquo;s call is being recorded. At this time, for opening remarks and introductions, I would like to turn the call over to Tejas Gala, Director of Investor Relations and Corporate Finance. Please go ahead.
Tejas Gala: Thank you. Good afternoon, and thank you for joining us. Speaking first today is Apple&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Tim Cook; and he&amp;rsquo;ll be followed by CFO, Luca Maestri.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN_2022_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/07/amzn_2022_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 21:06:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/07/amzn_2022_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Thank you for standing by. Good day, everyone, and welcome to the Amazon.com Q2 2022 Financial Results Teleconference. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the presentation, we will conduct a question-and-answer session. Today&amp;rsquo;s call is being recorded. For opening remarks, I will be turning the call over to the Director of Investor Relations, Dave Fildes. Please go ahead.
Dave Fildes: Hello, and welcome to our Q2 2022 financial results conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG_2022_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/07/goog_2022_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 20:47:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/07/goog_2022_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Welcome, everyone, and thank you for standing by for the Alphabet Inc. Second Quarter 2022 Earnings Call. At this time all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the speakers’ presentation, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] I would now like to hand the conference over to your speaker today, Jim Friedland, Director of Investor Relations. Please go ahead.
Jim Friedland: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to Alphabet’s second quarter 2022 earnings conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2022_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/07/msft_2022_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 20:07:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/07/msft_2022_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Greetings, and welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2022 Fourth Quarter Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. A question-and-answer session will follow the formal presentation. [Operator Instructions] As a reminder, this conference is being recorded. It is now my pleasure to introduce your host, Brett Iversen, Vice President of Investor Relations. Thank you. You may begin.
Brett Iversen: Good afternoon, and thank you for joining us today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSLA_2022_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/07/tsla_2022_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 22:04:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/07/tsla_2022_q2/</guid>
      <description>Martin Viecha: Good afternoon, everyone and welcome to Tesla’s Second Quarter 2022 Q&amp;amp;A Webcast. My name is Martin Viecha, VP of Investor Relations; and I am joined today by Elon Musk, Zachary Kirkhorn and a number of other executives. Our Q2 results were announced at about 3:00 p.m. Central Time in the update deck we published at the same link as this webcast. During this call, we will discuss our business outlook and make forward-looking statements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2023_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/05/nvda_2023_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 19:24:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/05/nvda_2023_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is David, and I&amp;rsquo;ll be your conference operator today. At this time, I&amp;rsquo;d like to welcome everyone to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s first quarter earnings call. Today&amp;rsquo;s conference is being recorded. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speaker’s remarks, there will be question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] Thank you. Simona Jankowski, you may begin your conference.
Simona Jankowski: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s conference call for the First Quarter of Fiscal 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN_2022_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/04/amzn_2022_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 20:27:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/04/amzn_2022_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Thank you for standing by. Good day, everyone, and welcome to the Amazon.com Q1 2022 Financial Results Teleconference. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the presentation, we will conduct a question-and-answer session. Today&amp;rsquo;s call is being recorded. For opening remarks, I will be turning the call over to the Director of Investor Relations, Dave Fildes. Please go ahead.
Dave Fildes: Hello, and welcome to our Q1 2022 financial results conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AAPL_2022_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/04/aapl_2022_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 19:21:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/04/aapl_2022_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good day and welcome to the Apple Q2 FY 2022 Earnings Conference Call. Today&amp;rsquo;s call is being recorded. At this time for opening remarks and introductions I would like to turn the call over to Tejas Gala, Director of Investor Relations and Corporate Finance. Please, go ahead.
Tejas Gala: Thank you. Good afternoon and thank you for joining us. Speaking first today is Apple&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Tim Cook; and he&amp;rsquo;ll be followed by CFO, Luca Maestri.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META_2022_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/04/meta_2022_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 22:03:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/04/meta_2022_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is France and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to the Meta First Quarter Earnings Conference Call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers’ remarks, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] The call will also be recorded. Thank you very much. Ms. Deborah Crawford, Meta’s Vice President of Investor Relations, you may begin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG_2022_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/04/goog_2022_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 21:59:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/04/goog_2022_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Welcome, everyone, and thank you for standing by for the Alphabet First Quarter 2022 Earnings Conference Call. [Operator Instructions] I&amp;rsquo;d now like to hand the conference over to your speaker today, Jim Friedland, Director of Investor Relations. Please go ahead.
James Friedland: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s first quarter 2022 earnings conference call. With us today are Sundar Pichai, Philipp Schindler and Ruth Porat. Now I&amp;rsquo;ll quickly cover the safe harbor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2022_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/04/msft_2022_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 21:20:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/04/msft_2022_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Ladies and gentlemen thank you for standing by. Welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2022 Third Quarter Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. A question-and-answer session will follow the formal presentation. [Operator Instructions] As a reminder, this conference is being recorded. It is now my pleasure to introduce your host, Brett Iversen, General Manager, Investor Relations. Thank you. You may begin.
Brett Iversen: Good afternoon and thank you for joining us today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSLA_2022_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/04/tsla_2022_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 21:44:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/04/tsla_2022_q1/</guid>
      <description>Martin Viecha: Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to Tesla’s First Quarter 2022 Q&amp;amp;A Webcast. My name is Martin Viecha, VP of Investor Relations, and I’m joined today by Elon Musk, Zachary Kirkhorn and a number of other executives. Our Q1 results were announced at about 3 p.m. Central Time in the update deck we published at the same link as this webcast. During this call, we will discuss our business outlook and make forward-looking statements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2022_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/02/nvda_2022_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 22:12:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/02/nvda_2022_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is David, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I&amp;rsquo;d like to welcome everyone to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s Fourth Quarter Earnings Call. Today&amp;rsquo;s conference is being recorded. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers’ remarks, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions]. Thank you. Simona Jankowski, you may begin your conference.
Simona Jankowski: Thank you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN_2021_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/02/amzn_2021_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 19:50:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/02/amzn_2021_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Thank you for standing by. Good day, everyone, and welcome to the Amazon.com Q4 2021 Financial Results Teleconference. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the presentation, we will conduct a question-and-answer session. Today’s call is being recorded. For opening remarks, I will be turning the call over to the Director of Investor Relations, Dave Fildes. Please go ahead.
Dave Fildes: Hello, and welcome to our Q4 2021 financial results conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META_2021_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/02/meta_2021_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 20:36:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/02/meta_2021_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Frans, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to the Meta Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2021 Earnings Conference Call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers’ remarks, there will be a question-and-answer session. . The call will be recorded. Thank you very much. Ms. Deborah Crawford, Facebook Vice President of Investor Relations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG_2021_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/02/goog_2021_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 21:11:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/02/goog_2021_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Welcome, everyone, and thank you for standing by for the Alphabet Fourth Quarter 2021 Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the speakers’ presentation, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions]. I&amp;rsquo;d now like to hand the conference over to your speaker today, Jim Friedland, Director of Investor Relations. Please go ahead.
James Friedland: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s fourth quarter 2021 earnings conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AAPL_2022_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/01/aapl_2022_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 20:19:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/01/aapl_2022_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good day, and welcome to the Apple Q1 FY 2022 Earnings Conference Call. Today&amp;rsquo;s call is being recorded. At this time, for opening remarks and introductions, I would like to turn the call over to Tejas Gala, Director of Investor Relations and Corporate Finance. Please go ahead.
Tejas Gala: Thank you. Good afternoon, and thank you for joining us. Speaking today first is Apple&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Tim Cook; and he&amp;rsquo;ll be followed by CFO, Luca Maestri.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSLA_2021_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/01/tsla_2021_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 21:21:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/01/tsla_2021_q4/</guid>
      <description>Martin Viecha: Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to Tesla&amp;rsquo;s Fourth Quarter 2021 Q&amp;amp;A Webcast. My name is Martin Viecha, Senior Director of Investor Relations, and I&amp;rsquo;m joined today by Elon Musk, Zachary Kirkhorn and a number of other executives. Our Q4 results were announced at about 3:00 p.m. Central Time in the update deck we published at the same link as this webcast. During this call, we will discuss our business outlook and make forward-looking statements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2022_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/01/msft_2022_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 20:51:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2022/01/msft_2022_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Greetings, and welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2022 Second Quarter Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. A question-and-answer session will follow the formal presentation. [Operator Instructions] As a reminder, this conference is being recorded. It is now my pleasure to introduce your host, Brett Iversen, General Manager, Investor Relations. Thank you. You may begin.
Brett Iversen: Good afternoon, and thank you for joining us today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN_2021_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/10/amzn_2021_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 23:14:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/10/amzn_2021_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Thank you for standing by. Good day, everyone, and welcome to the amazon.com Q3 2021 Financial Results Teleconference. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the presentation, we will conduct a question-and-answer session. Today&amp;rsquo;s call is being recorded. For opening remarks, I&amp;rsquo;ll be turning the call over to Director of Investor Relations, Dave Fildes. Please go ahead.
Dave Fildes: Hello, and welcome to our Q3 2021 financial results conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AAPL_2021_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/10/aapl_2021_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 21:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/10/aapl_2021_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good day, and welcome to the Apple Q4 Fiscal Year 2021 Earnings Conference Call. Today’s call is being recorded. At this time, for opening remarks and introductions, I would like to turn the call over to Tejas Gala, Director of Investor Relations and Corporate Finance. Please go ahead.
Tejas Gala: Thank you. Good afternoon, and thank you for joining us. Speaking today first is Apple’s CEO, Tim Cook; and he’ll be followed by CFO, Luca Maestri.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2022_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/10/msft_2022_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 21:19:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/10/msft_2022_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Greetings and welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2022, First-Quarter earnings conference call. As a reminder, this conference is being recorded. It is now my pleasure to introduce your host, Brett Iversen, General Manager and Investor Relations. Thank you, you may begin.
Brett Iversen: Good afternoon, and thank you for joining us today. On the call with me are Satya Nadella, Chairman Chief Executive Officer, Amy Hood, Chief Financial Officer, Alice Jalla, Chief Accounting Officer, and Keith Dolliver, Deputy General Counsel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG_2021_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/10/goog_2021_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 20:10:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/10/goog_2021_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Welcome everyone, and thank you for standing by for the Alphabet Q3 2021 Earnings C conference Call. At this time, all participants are in listen-only mode. After the speaker presentation, there will be a question-and-answer session. I&amp;rsquo;d now like to turn the conference over to your speaker today, Jim Friedland, Director of Investor Relations. Please go ahead.
Jim Friedland: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s third quarter 2021 earnings conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META_2021_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/10/meta_2021_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 21:08:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/10/meta_2021_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is France, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to the Facebook Third Quarter 2021 earnings conference call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speaker’s remarks, there will be a question-and-answer session. keypad. This call will be recorded. Thank you very much. Ms. Deborah Crawford Facebook Vice President of Investor Relations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSLA_2021_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/10/tsla_2021_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 21:58:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/10/tsla_2021_q3/</guid>
      <description>Lars Moravy:
Vice President of Vehicle Engineering:
Martin Viecha : Good afternoon, everyone and welcome to Tesla &amp;rsquo;s Third Quarter 2021 Q&amp;amp;A webcast. My name is Martin Viecha, Senior Director of Investor Relations and I&amp;rsquo;m joined today by our CFO, Zachary Kirkhorn, and our Senior VP, Drew Baglino, as well as other executives. Our Q3 results were announced at about 3 p.m. Central Time in the Update deck we published at the same link as this webcast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2022_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/08/nvda_2022_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 22:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/08/nvda_2022_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Mel, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s Second Quarter Earnings Call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers&amp;rsquo; remarks, there will be a question and answer session. [Operator Instructions] Thank you. Simona Jankowski, you may begin your conference.
Simona Jankowski: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN_2021_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/07/amzn_2021_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 20:51:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/07/amzn_2021_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Thank you for standing by. Good day, everyone, and welcome to the amazon.com Q2 2021 Financial Results, Teleconference. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the presentation, we will conduct a question-and-answer session. Today&amp;rsquo;s call is being recorded. For opening remarks, I will be turning the call over to Director of Investor Relations, Mr. Dave Fildes. Please go ahead.
Dave Fildes: Hello, and welcome to our Q2 2021 financial results conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META_2021_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/07/meta_2021_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:20:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/07/meta_2021_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is France [ph], and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to the Facebook Second Quarter 2021 Earnings Conference Call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers&amp;rsquo; remarks, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] This call will be recorded. We thank you very much. Ms. Deborah Crawford, Facebook&amp;rsquo;s Vice President of Investor Relations, you may begin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AAPL_2021_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/07/aapl_2021_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 23:13:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/07/aapl_2021_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good day, and welcome to the Apple Q3 FY 2021 Earnings Conference Call. Today&amp;rsquo;s call is being recorded. At this time, for opening remarks and introductions, I&amp;rsquo;d like to turn the call over to Tejas Gala, Director, Investor Relations and Corporate Finance. Please go ahead.
Tejas Gala: Thank you. Good afternoon, and thank you for joining us. Speaking first today is Apple&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Tim Cook, and he&amp;rsquo;ll be followed by CFO, Luca Maestri.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG_2021_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/07/goog_2021_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 22:55:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/07/goog_2021_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Welcome, everyone. Thank you for standing by for the Alphabet Second Quarter 2021 Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the speakers’ presentation, there will be a question-and-answer session. I would now like to hand the conference over to your speaker today, Jim Friedland, Director of Investor Relations. Please go ahead.
Jim Friedland: Thank you. Good afternoon everyone and welcome to Alphabet’s second quarter earnings conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2021_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/07/msft_2021_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 21:36:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/07/msft_2021_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Greetings, and welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2021 Fourth Quarter Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. A question-and-answer session will follow the formal presentation. [Operator Instructions] As a reminder, this conference is being recorded. It is now my pleasure to introduce your host, Brett Iversen, General Manager of Investor Relations. Thank you. You may begin.
Brett Iversen: Good afternoon and thank you for joining us today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSLA_2021_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/07/tsla_2021_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 23:09:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/07/tsla_2021_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good day and thank you for standing by. Welcome to the Tesla Second Quarter 2021 Financial results and Q&amp;amp;A webcast. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the speakers&amp;rsquo; presentation, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator instructions] Please, be advised that today&amp;rsquo;s conference is being recorded. [Operator instructions] I would now like to hand the conference over to your speaker today, Martin Viecha, Senior Director of Investor Relations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2022_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/05/nvda_2022_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 23:46:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/05/nvda_2022_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Sumitra, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to the NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s Financial Results Conference Call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers&amp;rsquo; remarks, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] Thank you. Simona Jankowski, you may begin your conference.
Simona Jankowski: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s conference call for the first quarter of fiscal 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN_2021_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/04/amzn_2021_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 23:15:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/04/amzn_2021_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Thank you for standing by. Good day, everyone, and welcome to the Amazon.com Q1 2021 Financial Results Teleconference. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the presentation, we will conduct a question-and-answer session. Today&amp;rsquo;s call is being recorded. For opening remarks, I will be turning the call over to Director of Investor Relations, Mr. Dave Fildes. Please go ahead.
Dave Fildes: Hello, and welcome to our Q1 2021 financial results conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AAPL_2021_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/04/aapl_2021_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 21:17:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/04/aapl_2021_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good day, and welcome to the Apple Q2 FY 2021 Earnings Conference Call. Today&amp;rsquo;s call is being recorded. At this time, for opening remarks and introductions, I&amp;rsquo;d like to turn the call over to Tejas Gala, Director, Investor Relations and Corporate Finance. Please go ahead.
Tejas Gala: Thank you. Good afternoon and thank you for joining us. Speaking first today is Apple&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Tim Cook, and he&amp;rsquo;ll be followed by CFO, Luca Maestri.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META_2021_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/04/meta_2021_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 21:04:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/04/meta_2021_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is France, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to Facebook First Quarter 2021 Earnings Conference Call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers’ remarks, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] This call will be recorded. Thank you very much. Ms. Deborah Crawford, Facebook&amp;rsquo;s Vice President of Investor Relations, you may begin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2021_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/04/msft_2021_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 23:42:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/04/msft_2021_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Greetings, and welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2021 Third Quarter Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. A question-and-answer session will follow the formal presentation. [Operator Instructions] And as a reminder, this conference is being recorded. It is now my pleasure to introduce your host, Brett Iversen, General Manager, Investor Relations. Thank you. You may begin.
Brett Iversen: Good afternoon, and thank you for joining us today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG_2021_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/04/goog_2021_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 23:05:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/04/goog_2021_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Welcome, everyone, and thank you for standing by for the Alphabet First Quarter 2021 Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the speakers’ presentation, there will be a question-and-answer session. I’d now like to hand the conference over to your speaker today, Jim Friedland, Director of Investor Relations. Please go ahead.
Jim Friedland: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to Alphabet’s first quarter 2021 earnings conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSLA_2021_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/04/tsla_2021_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 00:59:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/04/tsla_2021_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good day, ladies and gentlemen, and thank you for standing by, and welcome to the Tesla First Quarter 2021 Results and Q&amp;amp;A Webcast. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the presentation, there will be a question-and-answer session. Please be advised that today’s conference is being recorded. [Operator Instructions] I will now hand the conference over to your speaker today, Martin Viecha, Senior Director of Investor Relations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2021_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/02/nvda_2021_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 23:44:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/02/nvda_2021_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Mariama, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s Financial Results Conference Call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers&amp;rsquo; remarks, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] Thank you. I will now turn the call over to Simona Jankowski, NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s Vice President of Investor Relations and Strategic Finance to begin the conference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN_2020_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/02/amzn_2020_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 23:25:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/02/amzn_2020_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Thank you for standing by. Good day, everyone and welcome to the Amazon.com Q4 2020 Financial Results Teleconference. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the presentation, we will conduct a question-and-answer session. Today’s call is being recorded. For opening remarks, I will be turning the call over to Director of Investor Relations, Dave Fildes. Please go ahead.
Dave Fildes: Hello and welcome to our Q4 2020 financial results conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG_2020_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/02/goog_2020_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 20:14:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/02/goog_2020_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Welcome, everyone, and thank you for standing by for the Alphabet Fourth Quarter 2020 Earnings Conference Call. . I would now like to hand the conference over to your speaker today, Jim Friedland, Director of Investor Relations. Please go ahead.
James Friedland: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s Fourth Quarter 2020 Earnings Conference Call. With us today are Sundar Pichai, Philipp Schindler and Ruth Porat. Now I&amp;rsquo;ll quickly cover the safe harbor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSLA_2020_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/01/tsla_2020_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 21:23:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/01/tsla_2020_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for standing by, and welcome to Tesla&amp;rsquo;s Q4 2020 Financial Results and Q&amp;amp;A Webcast. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the speaker presentation, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] Please be advised that today&amp;rsquo;s conference is being recorded. [Operator Instructions] I would now like to hand the conference over to your speaker, Mr. Martin Viecha, Senior Director of Investor Relations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META_2020_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/01/meta_2020_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 20:50:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/01/meta_2020_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Mike, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to the Facebook Fourth Quarter and Full-Year 2020 Earnings Conference Call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers’ remarks, there’ll be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] This call will be recorded. Thank you very much. Ms. Deborah Crawford, Facebook’s Vice President of Investor Relations, you may begin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AAPL_2021_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/01/aapl_2021_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 20:48:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/01/aapl_2021_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good day, and welcome to the Apple Q1 Fiscal Year 2021 Earnings Conference Call. Today&amp;rsquo;s call is being recorded. At this time, for opening remarks and introductions, I would like to turn the call over to Tejas Gala, Director of Investor Relations and Corporate Finance. Please go ahead.
Tejas Gala: Thank you. Good afternoon and thank you for joining us. Speaking first today is Apple&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Tim Cook, and he&amp;rsquo;ll be followed by CFO, Luca Maestri.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2021_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/01/msft_2021_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 22:56:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2021/01/msft_2021_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Greetings, and welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2021 Second Quarter Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. A brief question-and-answer session will follow the formal presentation. [Operator Instructions] As a reminder, this conference is being recorded. It is now my pleasure to introduce your host, Mike Spencer, General Manager, Investor Relations. Thank you, sir. You may begin.
Michael Spencer: Good afternoon, and thank you for joining us today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2021_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/11/nvda_2021_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 21:53:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/11/nvda_2021_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Jason, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to NVIDIA’s Third Quarter Financial Results Conference Call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers’ remarks, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] Thank you. Simona Jankowski, you may begin your conference.
Simona Jankowski: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone and welcome to NVIDIA’s conference call for the third quarter of fiscal 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META_2020_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/10/meta_2020_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 00:56:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/10/meta_2020_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Mike and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to the Facebook Third Quarter 2020 Earnings Conference Call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers’ remarks there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] This call will be recorded. Thank you very much. Ms. Deborah Crawford, Facebook’s Vice President of Investor Relations, you may begin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AAPL_2020_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/10/aapl_2020_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 23:40:53 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/10/aapl_2020_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good day everyone and welcome to the Apple Inc. Fourth Quarter Fiscal Year 2020 Earnings Conference Call. Today’s call is being recorded. At this time for opening remarks and introductions, I would like to turn things over to Tejas Gala, Senior Analyst, Corporate Finance and Investor Relations. Please go ahead, sir.
Tejas Gala: Thank you. Good afternoon and thank you for joining us. Speaking first today is Apple’s CEO, Tim Cook, and he will be followed by CFO, Luca Maestri.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG_2020_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/10/goog_2020_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 23:16:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/10/goog_2020_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for standing by, and welcome to the Alphabet Third Quarter 2020 Earnings Conference Call. At this time all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the speakers presentation, there will be a question-and-answer session. . I&amp;rsquo;d now like to hand the conference over to your speaker today, Jim Friedland, Director of Investor Relations. Please go ahead.
James Friedland: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s third quarter 2020 earnings conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN_2020_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/10/amzn_2020_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 22:40:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/10/amzn_2020_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Thank you for standing by. Good day, everyone and welcome to the Amazon.com Q3 2020 Financial Results Teleconference. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the presentation, we will conduct a question-and-answer session. Today&amp;rsquo;s call is being recorded. For opening remarks, I will be turning the call over to Head of Investor Relations, Dave Fildes. Please go ahead.
Dave Fildes: Hello and welcome to our Q3 2020 financial results conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2021_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/10/msft_2021_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 21:15:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/10/msft_2021_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Greetings, and welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2021 First Quarter Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. A question-and-answer session will follow the formal presentation. [Operator Instructions] As a reminder, this conference is being recorded. It is now my pleasure to introduce your host, Michael Spencer, General Manager, Investor Relations. Thank you. You may begin.
Michael Spencer: Good afternoon and thank you for joining us today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSLA_2020_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/10/tsla_2020_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 23:00:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/10/tsla_2020_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for standing by, and welcome to the Tesla Q3 2020 Financial Results and Q&amp;amp;A Webcast. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the speaker presentation, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] I would now like to hand the conference over to your speaker, Mr. Martin Viecha, Senior Director of Investor Relations. Please, go ahead, sir.
Martin Viecha: Thank you, Sherry, and good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to Tesla&amp;rsquo;s third quarter 2020 Q&amp;amp;A webcast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2021_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/08/nvda_2021_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 02:03:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/08/nvda_2021_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is David and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to NVIDIA’s Financial Results Conference Call. [Operator Instructions] Thank you. Simona Jankowski, you may begin your conference.
Simona Jankowski: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone and welcome to NVIDIA’s conference call for the second quarter of fiscal 2021. With me on the call today from NVIDIA are Jensen Huang, President and Chief Executive Officer and Colette Kress, Executive Vice President and Chief Financial Officer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AAPL_2020_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/07/aapl_2020_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 23:35:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/07/aapl_2020_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good day, everyone. Welcome to the Apple Incorporated Third Quarter Fiscal Year 2020 Earnings Conference Call. Today&amp;rsquo;s call is being recorded. At this time, for opening remarks and introductions, I would like to turn things over to Mr. Tejas Gala, Senior Manager, Corporate Finance and Investor Relations. Please go ahead, sir.
Tejas Gala: Thank you. Good afternoon and thank you for joining us. Speaking first today is Apple&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Tim Cook; and he&amp;rsquo;ll be followed by CFO, Luca Maestri.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN_2020_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/07/amzn_2020_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 22:42:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/07/amzn_2020_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Thank you for standing by. Good day, everyone, and welcome to the Amazon.com Q2 2020 Financial Results Teleconference. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the presentation, we will conduct a question-and-answer session. Today’s call is being recorded. For opening remarks, I will be turning the call over to Director of Investor Relations, David Fildes. Please go ahead.
David Fildes: Hello, and welcome to our Q2 2020 financial results conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META_2020_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/07/meta_2020_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 22:24:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/07/meta_2020_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Mike and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to the Facebook Second Quarter 2020 Earnings Conference Call. All lines have been placed on mute to prevent any background noise. After the speakers’ remarks, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] This call will be recorded. Thanks very much. Ms. Deborah Crawford, Facebook’s Vice President of Investor Relations, you may begin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG_2020_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/07/goog_2020_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 21:03:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/07/goog_2020_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for standing by, and welcome to the Alphabet Second Quarter 2020 Earnings Conference Call. . I&amp;rsquo;d now like to hand the conference over to your speaker today, Jim Friedland, Director of Investor Relations. Please go ahead.
James Friedland: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s second quarter 2020 earnings conference call. With us today are Sundar Pichai and Ruth Porat. Now I&amp;rsquo;ll quickly cover the safe harbor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSLA_2020_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/07/tsla_2020_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 22:28:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/07/tsla_2020_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for standing by and welcome to Tesla’s Q2 2020 Financial Results Q&amp;amp;A and Webcast. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the speaker presentation, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] I would now like to hand the conference over to your speaker, Mr. Martin Viecha, Senior Director for Investor Relations. Please go ahead, sir.
Martin Viecha: Thank you, Sherry, and good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to Tesla’s second quarter 2020 Q&amp;amp;A webcast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2020_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/07/msft_2020_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 21:28:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/07/msft_2020_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Greetings, and welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2020 Fourth Quarter Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. A question-and-answer session will follow the former presentation. [Operator Instructions] As a reminder, this conference is being recorded. It is now my pleasure to introduce your host, Mike Spencer, General Manager and Investor Relations for Microsoft. Thank you, sir. You may begin.
Mike Spencer: Good afternoon and thank you for joining us today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2021_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/05/nvda_2021_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 04:29:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/05/nvda_2021_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Josh, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s Financial Results Conference call. [Operator Instructions]. Simona Jankowski, you may begin your conference.
Simona Jankowski: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s conference call for the first quarter of fiscal 2021. With me on the call today from NVIDIA are Jensen Huang, President and Chief Executive Officer; and Colette Kress, Executive Vice President and Chief Financial Officer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN_2020_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/04/amzn_2020_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 22:46:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/04/amzn_2020_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good day everyone and welcome to the Amazon.com Q1 2020 financial results teleconference. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the presentation we will conduct a question and answer session. Today&amp;rsquo;s call is being recorded. For opening remarks, I will be turning the call over to Director of Investor Relations, Shelly Kay Pfeiffer. Please go ahead.
Shelly Kay Pfeiffer: Hello and welcome to our Q1 2020 financial results conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AAPL_2020_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/04/aapl_2020_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 21:51:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/04/aapl_2020_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good day everyone. Welcome to the Apple Incorporated Second Quarter Fiscal Year 2020 Earnings Conference Call. Today’s call is being recorded. At this time for opening remarks and introductions, I would like to turn the call over to Mr. Tejas Gala, Senior Manager, Corporate Finance and Investor Relations. Please go ahead.
Tejas Gala: Thank you. Good afternoon and thank you for joining us. Speaking first today is Apple’s CEO, Tim Cook, and he will be followed by CFO, Luca Maestri.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META_2020_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/04/meta_2020_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 23:56:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/04/meta_2020_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon, my name is Mike and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to the Facebook First Quarter 2020 Earnings Conference Call. [Operator Instructions] Ms. Deborah Crawford, Facebook&amp;rsquo;s Vice President of Investor Relations, you may begin.
Deborah Crawford: Thank you. Good afternoon and welcome to Facebook&amp;rsquo;s first quarter 2020 earnings conference call. Joining me today to discuss our results are Mark Zuckerberg, CEO; Sheryl Sandberg, COO; and Dave Wehner, CFO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSLA_2020_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/04/tsla_2020_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 23:20:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/04/tsla_2020_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for standing by, and welcome to Tesla&amp;rsquo;s Q1 2020 Financial Results and Q&amp;amp;A Webcast. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the speaker presentation, there will be a question-and-answer session. [Operator Instructions] Please be advised that today&amp;rsquo;s conference is being recorded. [Operator Instructions] I would now like to hand the conference over to your speaker, Mr. Martin Viecha, Senior Director for Investor Relations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2020_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/04/msft_2020_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 23:01:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/04/msft_2020_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Greetings, and welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2020 Third Quarter Earnings Conference Call. [Operator Instructions]. As a reminder, this conference is being recorded. I would now like to turn the conference over to your host, Mr. Mike Spencer, General Manager of Investor Relations for Microsoft. Thank you. You may begin.
Michael Spencer: Good afternoon, and thank you for joining us today. On the call with me are Satya Nadella, Chief Executive Officer; Amy Hood, Chief Financial Officer; Frank Brod, Chief Accounting Officer; and Keith Dolliver, Deputy General Counsel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG_2020_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/04/goog_2020_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 23:46:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/04/goog_2020_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for standing by. And welcome to the Alphabet First Quarter 2020 Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. After the speakers’ presentation, there will be a question-and-answer session. I would now like to hand the conference over to your speaker today, Jim Friedland, Director of Investor Relations. Please go ahead.
Jim Friedland: Thank you, Candice. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to Alphabet’s first quarter 2020 earnings conference call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2020_Q4</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/02/nvda_2020_q4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 21:46:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/02/nvda_2020_q4/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Christina and I&amp;rsquo;m your conference operator today. Welcome to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s financial results conference call. All lines have been placed on mute. After the speakers&amp;rsquo; remarks, there will be question-and-answer period. [Operator Instructions] Thank you. I&amp;rsquo;ll now turn the call over to Simona Jankowski, Vice President of Investor Relations, to begin your conference.
Simona Jankowski: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s conference call for the fourth quarter of fiscal 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2020_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/01/msft_2020_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 21:38:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/01/msft_2020_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2020 Second Quarter Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. A brief question-and-answer session will follow the formal presentation. [Operator Instructions] As a reminder, this conference is being recorded. I would like to turn the call over to Mike Spencer, General Manager of Investor Relations. Thank you. Please proceed.
Mike Spencer: Good afternoon and thank you for joining us today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AAPL_2020_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/01/aapl_2020_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 21:35:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2020/01/aapl_2020_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good day, everyone. Welcome to the Apple Incorporated First Quarter Fiscal Year 2020 Earnings Conference Call. Today&amp;rsquo;s conference is being recorded. At this time for opening remarks and introductions, I would like to turn the call over to Tejas Gala, Senior Analyst, Corporate Finance and Investor Relations. Please go ahead.
Tejas Gala: Thank you. Good afternoon, and thank you for joining us. Speaking first today is Apple&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Tim Cook, and he&amp;rsquo;ll be followed by CFO, Luca Maestri.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2020_Q3</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2019/11/nvda_2020_q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 21:12:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2019/11/nvda_2020_q3/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Christina, and I&amp;rsquo;m your conference operator for today. Welcome to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s Financial Results Conference Call. [Operator Instructions]. I&amp;rsquo;ll now turn the call over to Simona Jankowski, Vice President of Investor Relations, to begin your conference.
Simona Jankowski: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s conference call for the third quarter of fiscal 2020. With me on the call today from NVIDIA are Jensen Huang, President and Chief Executive Officer; and Colette Kress, Executive Vice President and Chief Financial Officer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT_2020_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2019/10/msft_2020_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 22:19:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2019/10/msft_2020_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Welcome to the Microsoft Fiscal Year 2020 First Quarter Earnings Conference Call. At this time, all participants are in a listen-only mode. A brief question-and-answer session will follow the formal presentation. [Operator Instructions] As a reminder, this conference is being recorded. I would like to turn the call over to Mike Spencer, General Manager of Investor Relations. Thank you. Please proceed.
Mike Spencer: Good afternoon. Thank you for joining us today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2020_Q2</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2019/08/nvda_2020_q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 08:42:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2019/08/nvda_2020_q2/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Christina, and I will be your conference operator today. Welcome to NVIDIA’s financial results conference call. [Operator Instructions] I will now turn the call over to Simona Jankowski from Investor Relations to begin your conference.
Simona Jankowski: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone and welcome to NVIDIA’s conference call for the second quarter of fiscal 2020. With me on the call today from NVIDIA are Jen-Hsun Huang, President and Chief Executive Officer and Colette Kress, Executive Vice President and Chief Financial Officer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA_2020_Q1</title>
      <link>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2019/05/nvda_2020_q1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 23:49:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://half-broken-engineer.github.io/2019/05/nvda_2020_q1/</guid>
      <description>Operator: Good afternoon. My name is Kristina, and I&amp;rsquo;ll be your conference operator today. Welcome to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s financial results conference call. All lines have been placed on mute. [Operator Instructions] I&amp;rsquo;ll now turn the call over to Simona Jankowski from Investor Relations to begin your conference.
Simona Jankowski: Thank you. Good afternoon, everyone. And welcome to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s conference call for the first quarter of fiscal 2020. With me on the call today from NVIDIA are Jen-Hsun Huang, President and Chief Executive Officer and Colette Kress, Executive Vice President and Chief Financial Officer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
